# **Josh Engert**

**IT Professional** 

I am aiming to gain a role that will challenge me and allow me to use my education, skills and past experiences in a way that is mutually beneficial to both myself and my employer, and allows for future professional growth and advancement.

**\** 0274202042

Kingsland, Auckland

#### **SKILLS**

Automation and Scripting

Windows/Linux/OSX

Programming

Hardware Set-up/Deployment

Team Leader/Problem Solver

**Customer Service Expertise** 

## **HOBBIES**

**DJing** 

Kickboxing

Card Collecting

**Rock Climbing** 

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

# **CCNA (Currently Studying)**

Cisco Systems

Embedded Systems
Essentials with Arm
Professional Certificate

# First Aid Level 1

St. Johns

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **New Era IT**

(2022 - Present)

Desktop/Network Support Technician

ACG Parnell's first point of contact for all IT and Network issues.

Required knowledge of the following:

- Scripting with Powershell
- Active Directory and Group Policy
- Office 365 Admin Suite
- Network Routing and Switching

# BurgerFuel, Mount Eden

(2015 - 2022)

Day Shift Manager

In charge of maintaining inventory level, contacting suppliers, and ensuring a high level of customer satisfaction while setting up the following night shift to run as smoothly as possible. Often called upon to solve IT issues by the franchisee.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Media Design School

(2018 - 2022)

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Currently Deferred, final year to complete.

## Rotorua Boys' High School

(2010 - 2014)

NCEA Level 3 (Merit Endorsed)

### **NOTABLE PROJECTS**

#### TinyDJ

A credit card sized DJ controller created using the ATMega32u4 microcontroller, that outputs MIDI signals to work with most major DJ software. Required understanding of electrical engineering concepts, and microcontrollers with analogue and digital input.

# Van-Go

A first person puzzle platformer developed in Unity using C#, based on the art style of Vincent van Gogh. In charge of the players movement mechanics and level design. Required a good understanding of geometry and physics.

## 3D Cloth Simulator

Used my knowledge of physics and geometry to create a cloth simulator with wind simulation in C++ utilising OpenGI.

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

References Available on Request